Erik Mayes

 $01000101\ 01110010\ 01101001\ 01101011\ 00100000\ 01001101\ 01100001\ 01111001\ 01100101\ 01110011$

321-301-3169 | emayes528@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/erik-mayes-4aa8a41b5/

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Strategic leader with 10+ years of experience managing large, diverse teams. Proven ability to motivate, mentor, and grow individuals. Transitioning from a successful career in retail to pursue a lifelong passion in computer science, with strong problem-solving skills and a drive for continuous learning.

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (Full-Time) | Fourth-Year Student | GPA: 3.5 Indian River State College Associate in Arts Degree | GPA 3.5 Orlando, FL 2024 - Present Fort Pierce, FL 2024

SKILLS

- **Proficient:** Java, C, SQL, Linux, Git
- Experience with: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Python

PROJECTS

MIPS Assembly Programming Project

- Developed a low-level program in MIPS assembly, including instruction formats, memory addressing, and control flow
- Gained hands-on experience with registers, stack operations and system calls

Harvard CS50x | Online

- https://github.com/emayes505/CS50-Harvard-Online-Course.git
- Flagship introductory computer science course

PERSONAL WEBSITE

Website: https://emayes505.github.io/erik mayes.github.io/index.html

Gained hands-on experience in designing, developing, and deploying responsive, user-friendly websites
using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and basic web hosting tools.

EMPLOYMENT

CVS Pharmacy

Retail Store Manager | Indialantic FL, Vero Beach FL

04/2018 - 01/2022

- Led, trained, and successfully developed teams totaling over 80 employees across multiple locations, improving performance, morale, and customer satisfaction.
- Ensured compliance with ADA regulations and company standards while driving performance in customer service, sales, margin, and employee training to meet key metric goals.

• Mentored and developed colleagues, by building their confidence and skills, directly guiding two into store manager roles and over 10+ others in achieving promotions across various levels.

Store Manager in Training | Melbourne, FL

08/2016 - 04/2018

- Developed strong leadership and team-building skills
- Supported daily operations by overseeing inventory management, implementing loss prevention strategies, and driving sales performance

Shift Supervisor / Cashier | Orlando, FL

07/2009 - 07/2016

HONORS/AWARDS

CVS Pharmacy | Indialantic FL, Vero Beach FL

Paragon Winner

2018

• Recognized for outstanding performance, leading the top-performing store among 15 locations in sales, customer service and operational efficiency metric